[Music]
best
recommendations elevate your life with
icici elevate the power of infinite
personalization and let the AI ​​do the
magic
[Music]
Elevate
24800 how long will it last unlimited
times increase If a
customer who has taken a policy of 10 lakhs brings 10 to our
center,
look at the center, look at the center,
so can I tell you about the product,
so my name is Amita Anand,
I will represent ICICI,
basically, what we met today, everything we
talked about earlier,
we talked about the Elevate product, so
this is the Elevate product, we are the
first time,
time, something is the first time, we mean,
this is the first product in the insurance industry with such features, who has not
launched it so far, those are the features that we talked about earlier,
Infinite Sum In Sure, the first
of its kind product which we have
Launched for health customers in
India this product is
designed which has a unique features which are there which primarily takes care
of the basic need of any customer
this product is designed keeping one
phenomenon in feature in mind that there
are various type of customers in the
market and everyone requires a product
which is suits him and has to be very
very unique or or or personalized in
nature we have designed this product
which is purely customizable you can
design customize as per your need and it
is backed by artificial intelligence
also more importantly it has got many
unique features which are industry first